Guide to the Mazzarella AIVS Collection of Librettos MSS.383
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series LXII: Verdi
  - Rigoletto, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Rigoletto (volume 36), undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    Performance Season/Date: Stagione 1879-80
  - Simon Boccanegra (volume 38), undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Performance Season/Date: Stagione 1880-81
  - Stiffelio (volume 39), 1850 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    Performance City and Venue: Grande Teatro Civico di Trieste
    Performance Season/Date: Stagione d'autunno 1850
  - Il Trovatore (volume 40), undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
    Performance Season/Date: 1853
  - Il Trovatore (volume 41), 1853 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    Performance City and Venue: Teatro di Apollo
    Performance Season/Date: Carnevale 1853
    Publication City and Publisher: Rome: presso Gio. Olivieri tipogr. dell' Univ. Rom.
  - Les Vepres Siciliennes (volume 42), 1855 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    Librettist: Scribe, M.M.; Duveyrier, Charles
    Performance City and Venue: Paris: Theatre de l'Academie imperiale de Musique
    Performance Season/Date: Juin 1855
    Publication City and Publisher: Paris: Michel Levy Freres
  - Les Vepres Siciliennes, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Librettist: Scribe, Eugene; Duveyrier, Charles
    Performance Season/Date: 1875-1876
  - Les Vepres Siciliennes, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Performance Season/Date: Carnevale 1908-1909
  - Viscardello [Rigoletto censored] (volume 37), undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Series LXIII: Wagner
  - Lohengrin, 1873 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    Librettist: Wagner, Riccardo
    Performance Season/Date: Carnevale e Quaresima 1872
    Publication City and Publisher: Milan: F. Lucca
  - Lohengrin, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Librettist: Wagner, Richard
    Publication City and Publisher: New York: Fred. Rullman, Inc.
  - Lohengrin, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Performance Season/Date: Spring 1881
  - Tannhauser, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Tristan and Isolde, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Performance Season/Date: 1886-1887